Guide to the Laura (Riding) Jackson and Schuyler B. Jackson collection, 1924-1991
Jackson, Laura (Riding) and Schuyler B., 1924-1991
- Series II. Diaries
  - A) Laura (Riding) Jackson Diaries
    - Diary, May 1-June 30, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Diary, July 1-Dec. 31, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Diary, July 19-Aug. 12, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Diary, July 21-July 30, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Diary, Oct. 27-Nov. 16, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Diary, Nov. 16-Dec. 4, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Diary, Dec. 4-Dec. 14, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Diary, Dec. 14-Dec. 23, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Diary, Dec. 24, 1971-Jan. 1, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Diary, May 9-May 18, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Diary, Oct.11-Dec. 2, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Diary, Mar. 22-Apr. 14, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Diary, Aug. 5-Sept. 4, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Diary, Sept. 5-Oct. 7, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Travel Diary, Oct. 7-Nov. 6, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Diary, Nov. 6-Dec. 7, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Diary, Dec.7-Dec. 31, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Diary, Dec. 31, 1975-Feb. 9, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Diary, July 8-Aug. 17, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Diary, Aug. 17-Sept. 22, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Diary, Sept. 22-Oct. 12, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Diary, Oct. 12-Nov. 10, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Diary, Nov. 7-Dec. 7, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Diary, Dec. 7-Jan. 1, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Diary, Jan. 1-Jan. 18, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Diary, Jan. 19-Feb. 5, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Diary, Feb. 5-Feb. 18, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Diary, Feb. 18-Mar. 4, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Diary, Mar. 4-Mar. 26, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Diary, Mar. 28, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Diary, Jan. 3-Feb. 2, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Diary, Aug. 9-Sept. 7, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Diary, Sept. 7-Oct. 8, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Diary, Oct. 8-Nov. 3, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Diary, Nov. 3-Nov. 18, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Diary, Nov. 29-Dec. 12, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Diary, Dec. 12, 1978-Jan. 1, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Diary, Jan. 1-Jan 23, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Diary, Jan. 23-Feb. 13, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Diary, July 4-Aug. 5, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Diary, Sept. 14-Nov. 4, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Diary, Apr. 15-June 14, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Diary, June 17-Aug. 13, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Diary, May 15-Aug. 4, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Diary, Feb. 10-May 7, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Diary, May 7, July 8, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Diary, Mar. 28-Apr. 29, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Diary, Apr. 29-June 23, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Diary, June 24-Aug. 8, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Diary, Aug. 8-Aug. 29, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Diary, Aug. 30-Sept. 22, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Diary, Sept. 23-Oct. 26, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Diary, Oct. 26-Nov. 16, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Diary, Nov. 16-Dec. 17, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Diary, Dec. 17-Dec. 19, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Travel Diary, Oct. 1-Oct. 19, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Travel Diary, Nov. 16-Nov. 29, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Travel Diary, July 20-July 28, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Travel Diary, Aug. 29-Oct. 1, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Travel Diary, Oct. 2-Oct. 22, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Travel Diary, Oct. 28-Nov. 9, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Diary, Jan. 1-May 14, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Diary, May 14-July 4, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Appointment book, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Diary, June 2-July 18, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Diary, Aug. 12-Sept. 6, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Diary, Sept. 7-Dec. 24, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Diary, Dec. 24, 1969-Mar. 16, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Diary, Mar. 16-Apr. 4, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Diary, Apr. 4-May 22, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Diary, July 30-Sept. 7, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Diary, Sept. 7-Oct. 18, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Diary, Oct. 18-Nov. 22, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Diary, Nov. 22-Dec. 26, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Diary, Dec. 27, 1970-Jan. 27, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Diary, Jan. 27-Feb. 27, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Diary, Feb. 28-Apr. 2, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Diary, Apr. 3-May 5, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Diary, May 5-June 3, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Diary, June 11-Aug. 2, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Diary, Aug. 3-Aug. 31, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Diary, Aug. 31-Sept. 30, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Diary, Sept. 30-Oct. 27, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Diary, Jan. 2-Jan. 13, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Diary, Jan. 13-Jan.25, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Diary, Jan. 25-Feb. 7, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Diary, Feb. 7-Feb. 18, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Diary, Feb. 18-Mar. 1, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Diary, Mar. 2-Mar. 8, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Diary, Mar. 8-Apr. 9, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Diary, Apr.7-June 9, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Diary, May 19-July 8, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Diary, July 8-Aug. 16, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Diary, Aug. 16-Sept. 25, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Diary, Sept. 26-Oct. 10, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Diary, Nov. 2-Nov. 9, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Diary, Nov. 9-Dec. 3, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Diary, Dec. 4, 1972-Jan. 4, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Diary, Jan 4-Feb. 7, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Diary, Feb. 7-Mar. 22, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Diary, Mar. 22-Apr. 20, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Diary, Apr. 30-May 20, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Diary, May 20-July 3, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Diary, Aug. 25-Sept. 14, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Diary, Nov. 4-Nov. 25, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Diary, Nov. 25-Dec. 10, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Diary, Dec. 11, 1973-Jan. 4, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Diary, Jan. 4-Feb. 9, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Diary, Feb. 10-Mar. 22, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Diary, Aug. 14-Aug. 19, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Diary, Aug. 19-Aug. 24, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Diary, Aug. 24-Oct. 16, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Diary, Oct. 16-Dec. 10, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Diary, Dec. 10-Dec. 18, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Diary, Dec. 18, 1974-Feb. 5, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Diary, Feb. 5-May 15, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Diary, May 22-June 17, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Diary, June 19-July 7, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Diary, Dec. 20-Jan. 29, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Diary, Aug. 9-Oct. 23, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Diary, Oct. 23-Oct. 30, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Diary, Feb. 2(?)-May 30, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Diary, May 31-July 31, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Diary, July 31-Aug. 8, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Diary, Apr. 1-May 1, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Diary, June 13-June 17, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Diary, June 19-Aug. 9, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Diary, Oct. 30-Nov. 15, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Diary, Feb. 16-Mar. 10, 1980? (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - B) Schuyler B. Jackson Diaries
    - Diary, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Diary, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Diary, Aug. 2-Oct. 20, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Diary, Oct. 21-Dec. 30, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Diary, Dec. 31, 1966-June 30, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Diary, July 1-Dec. 31, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Diary, Jan. 1-July 4, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Series III. Correspondence
  - A) Laura (Riding) Jackson
    - Incoming
      - Letter record and correspondence notes, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Unidentified correspondents, 1926-1972 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Abels, Cyrilli (Literary agent), Aug. 22, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Abrams, Al, Sept. 4, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Harry N. Abrams, Inc., Sept. 24, 1987-Oct. 12, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Abrams, Mary G., Dec. 17, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Academy of American Poets, Apr. 1 to July 28, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Acumen Magazine, 1986 or 1987 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Adams, Barbara, Feb. 22, 1976-Mar. 26, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Addy, William J., 1982? to Nov. 3, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Albuquerque National Bank, Oct. 22, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Aldridge, Lucie, June 25, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Alfred A. Knopf, Inc., See: Knopf (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Allen, Doris Day, Feb. 16, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Allen, Robert F., ca. 1973 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - George Allen & Unwin, Nov. 5, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - American Biographical Institute, Oct. 15, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - American Book Review, Aug. 1, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - American Council of Learned Societies, Apr. 30-Dec. 29, 1975, See also: correspondence from ACLS in Series VII. Other Activities. The Wabasso Development Project (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - American Literature, Mar. 24, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - American Scholar, Aug. 31-Dec. 22, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - AMS Press, July 24-Oct. 23, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Anderson, Lorna, Jan. 17 to Mar. 10, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Andrew, Prudence, Oct. 8-Oct. 9, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Annis, J. W., Mar. 20, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Annual Bibliography of English Language and Literature, Oct. 17, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Ansill, Jay, Mar. 27, 1985-Sept. 25, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Antaeus. The Ecco Press, Apr. 5, 1972-Apr. 14, 1984, See also: Halpern, Daniel (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Antell-Cohen, Polly [Esther], Dec. 2, 1963-Mar. 6, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Appel, Paul (Publisher/Bookseller), Sept. 21, 1969-May 9, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Ardis, Sept. 22, 1979-Jan. 30, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - The Ark, Oct. 22, 1978-Nov. 10, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Art and Literature: An International Review, Oct. 12, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Aryan Path, June 20, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Ashbery, John, June 7, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - The Athlone Press of the University of London, Mar. 25, 1970-Sept. 16, 1980, See also: Oxford University Press. See also: letter to Athlone Press, Sept. 25, 1971 in Series IV. Literary Manuscripts. Published Works. Major Works [concerns The Telling] (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Atlantic Monthly, Dec. 16, 1971-Mar. 26, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Atsumi, Ikuko Sato, Aug. 27, 1975-Dec. 15, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - ATT, June 16, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - The Authors' Guild, May 27, 1975-Oct. 18, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Authors Take Sides on the Falklands, June 8, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Julian Bach, Jr., Literary Agency, Apr. 6-Apr. 22, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Bafalis, L. A. [Skip], Feb. 12, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Bailey, Richard W., Sept. 28, 1987-May 6, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Baker, Deborah, Nov. 14-Dec. 12, 1988, See also: Overlook Press (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Ball, [Wizzy], Sept. 8, 1968-Feb. 12, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Bank of Las Vegas, Aug. 22, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Virginia Barber Literary Agency, Inc., Dec. 21, 1983, Nov. 5, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Bardsley, Sheila, Nov. 15, 1968-June 7, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Barker, Arthur, Sept. 21, 1932-Sept. 3, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Barker, Pauline, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Barnett, Anthony, Jan. 3-May 25, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Barnett, Steven, Sept. 6,-Oct. 7, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Barnhouse, Nancy, Aug. 3, 1985-May 15, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Barrett, Ken, Mar 7-Dec 12, 1933 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Basic Books, Dec. 15, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Basil Blackwell Publisher, Nov. 4, 1976-May 4, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - BBC, See: British Broadcasting Corporation (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Beck, Ella, Dec. 21, 1974-1976? (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Beck, Mildred, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Beil, Joanna, Feb. 1, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Bell, Quentin, Feb. 13, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Bergstrom, Alice, Dec. 13, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Berndt, Mary C., Dec. 1976-Dec. 29, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Beston, John, Feb. 7, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Bettelheim, Wilhelm, Nov. 21, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Birch, Robert L., n.d. (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Birch, Robert L., n.d. (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - A&C Black, July 18, 1974-Aug. 19, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Black Swan Books, Feb. 15, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Blitch, Faye, Apr. 2, 1979-June 10, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Blue Buildings, 1978? (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Blue Cross, Blue Shield of Florida, June 6, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Boa Editions, Sept. 4, 1979-Oct. 18, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - The Booklist, Oct. 31, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Books & Co., Mar. 1, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Booth, Helen Mayers, Aug. 25, 1968-Feb. 2, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Georges Borchardt, Literary Agent, Oct. 31, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Boston University Libraries, July 2, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Boudin, Jean, Dec. 2, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Bowles, Gloria, Dec. 23, 1976-Mar. 13, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Bowman, Margaret [Maggy], Jan. 24, 1979-Apr. 28, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Marion Boyars Publishers, May 13, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Boys' and Girls' High School, Mar. 25, 1977-Oct. 14, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Bradford, Yorks (City Police Office), May 17, 1934-Nov. 2, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Brickel, Rose, Oct. 31, 1969-Nov. 3, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - British Broadcasting Corporation, Jan. 12, 1962-June 28, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Brock, Van K., Feb. 19-Apr. 29, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Brodhurst, Gwen, Sept. 3, 1985-Jan. 26, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Bronowski, Jacob, See: Roberts, Eirlys (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Brooks, Cleanth, Mar. 5, 1960-June 15, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Brooks, Marshall, Aug. 31-Sept. 27, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Brophy, Anna, 1975-1980 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Brown, Andrea, Oct. 8, 1979-Mar. 8, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Brown, Carol, Nov. 27, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Brown University, Development, Sept. 11, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Bruccoli Clark, Inc., Dec. 8, 1985-Mar. 11, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Buchanan, George, Mar. 13, 1959-Aug. 30, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Buergler, David, Feb. 6, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Burns, Albert See: the Albert Burns-Robert Sproat-Laura (Riding) Jackson Correspondence, Collection # 6300 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Butler, Sherman, Dec. 1974-Sept. 17, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Butts, Bill, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Cabral, Edward, 1982, Feb. 11, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Cambridge University Press, Sept. 15, 1970-Aug. 13, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Cameron, Esther [Beatrice], Mar. 16, 1973, Aug. 20, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Jonathan Cape, Ltd., May 1-Aug. 21, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Caraion, Ion, ca. 1981 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Carboni, Tom, Nov. 19, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Carcanet New Press, Oct. 29, 1977-Nov. 29, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 2)
        - Carcanet New Press, Oct. 29, 1977-Nov. 29, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 2)
        - Carcanet New Press, Jan. 3, 1980-Nov. 3, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 3)
        - Carcanet New Press, Jan. 4, 1982-Dec. 19, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 4)
        - Carcanet New Press, Jan. 10, 1984-May 29, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 5)
        - Carcanet New Press, May 30, 1985-Sept. 30, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 6)
        - Carcanet New Press, Oct. 13, 1986-June 1, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Carey, Michael V., Feb. 5, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Carnegie Fund for Authors, June 17, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Carpenter, Ted, Oct. 4, 1960, Nov. 27, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Carter, Gwendolen M., Aug. 12, 1977-Mar. 6, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Carter, Kathryn L., Feb. 11, 1970-Dec. 1976 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Cassell & Co., Oct. 5, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Cassidy, Naomi, Sept. 11, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Cassidy, Victor M., Mar.31, 1973-Feb. 17, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Cassidy, Victor M., Feb. 19, 1976-ca.Sept. 1983 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Cattanach, Bernice, Sept. 4, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Caudill, Darleen and Shaler, Apr. 24, 1972- Nov. 21, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Cavalier, Gertrude (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Cave, Roderick (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Chambers Publishers (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Chancen. Tidsskrift for Litteratur (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Chapman, Gerald (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Chatto & Windus (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Chelsea, See also: Series III. Correspondence, C) Correspondence, Sonia Raiziss to Laura (Riding) Jackson and to Schuyler B. Jackson (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Chesser, Georgia Mae, Nov. 3, 1969-July 31, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Chiles, Lawton, Mar. 18, 1976-Sept. 30, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Chilver, Sally, See: Series III. Correspondence, C) Formerly Restricted Correspondence, E.M. (Sally) Chilver (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Chisholm, Anne, June 26-July 10, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Christmas messages [selections], Jan. 1974 Notes by L(R)J identifying correspondents (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Christmas messages, ca. 1970-1973 (Box 16, Folder 2-4)
      - Civilta' delle Macchine, Apr. 30-Oct. 22, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Clark, Alan, See: Series III. Correspondence C) Formerly Restricted Correspondence, Alan Clark (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Clem, Chester, Mar. 19-Oct. 30, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Cohen, Joseph, July 30-Oct. 23, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Columbia University Press, Nov. 6, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Columbia University Press, Nov. 6, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Common Cause, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Comparative Literature Studies, Dec. 7, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Condolences sent upon death of SBJ [L(R)J's notes], July 30, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Sympathy cards, sender unidentified [with list of funeral attendees?], 1968 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Sympathy cards, sender identified, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Conjunctions, Nov. 22, 1980-Apr. 9, 1986., See also: Morrow, Bradford (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Conover, Ann, Harold, and Mae, July or Aug. 1968-1988 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Conrad, K. H., Jan. 31, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Constable, Feb 3, 1934-June 9, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Contact/II, See: Kenny, Maurice (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Contemporary Authors. Autobiography Series. See: Zadrozny, Mark (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Continuum Books., See: The Seabury Press (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Cornell University (Box 17, Folder 7)
        - Alumni Affairs, Office of, May 13, 1971-July 30, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 7)
        - Dean, Arthur, Jan. 21 and Feb. 7, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 7)
        - Class of '22, Mar. 19, 1972-Aug. 13, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 7)
        - Cornell Alumni Association, Apr. 14, 1972-Apr. 16, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 7)
        - Cornell University Libraries, Aug. 21, 1964-Mar. 21, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 7)
        - Cornell University Library. Department of Rare Books, Nov. 12, 1963-Dec. 17, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 8)
        - Cornell University Library. Department of Rare Books, Jan. 13, 1972-Oct. 16, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 9)
        - Cornell University Press, Sept. 3, 1968-Jan. 27, 1983, See also: Fincher, Evelyn Davis (Box 17, Folder 10)
        - President, Office of the, Dec. 1988 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Cotton, John, Oct. 27, 1970-Apr. 10, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Creative Age Press, Jan. 25-Mar. 14, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Critical Inquiry (University of Chicago), Feb. 20-May 14, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Critical Quarterly (University of Manchester), Nov. 11, 1981, Mar. 5, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Thomas Y. Crowell Company, Dec. 11, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Thomas Y. Crowell Company, Dec. 11, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Cruse (The National Organization for the Widowed and Their Children), June 18, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Cuadra, Jolico, Nov. 1, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Cubbler, Roy W., Oct. 9, 1978-Feb. 8, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Cullup, Michael, June 30, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Daedalus Books, Mar. 23, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Dall'Asta, Eberhard, Mar. 15, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Danmarks Radio, Dec. 28, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Daves, Joan, May 20, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Davie, Richard, 1986? (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Davis, Mae Nella, Dec. 1971-Dec. 1978 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Davis, Marian and Lillian, Dec. 1975 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Davis, Matt, Apr. 14, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Davis, Robert Gorham, Nov. 30, 1973-Oct. 3, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Davison, Peter, Mar. 3, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Davy, Charles, July 9, 1971-May 14, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Delaware, University of, Nov. 15, 1985-Jan. 28, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Deligne, Joelle, Aug. 1, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - J M Dent & Sons, May 28, 1943-June 13, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Denver Quarterly: A Journal of Modern Culture (University of Denver, CO), Jan. 2, 1973-Oct. 11, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - de Palchi, Alfredo, Apr. 1976-Apr. 6, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Department of Health, Education and Welfare, Vero Beach, Apr. 15, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Derus, Kenneth, June 14, 1984-July 19, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Dial Press, Sept. 11, 1980-Aug. 27, 1984, See also: McCullough, Frances (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Dickins, A. S. M., Mar. 2, 1976-May 5, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Dictionary of International Biography, Apr. 14, 1969-Sept. 2, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Doctors' Clinic, Feb. 23, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Doddridge, Elizabeth [Betty], June 24, 1970-Aug. 7, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Dominguez, Dionicio, Lizzie, and Bella, Aug. 29, 1968-Feb. 26, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Doner, Kathy, June 24, 1984-Nov. 26, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Donoghue, Denis, June 29, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Dorsett, Thomas, July 16, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Doubleday, Sept. 3, 1970-Dec. 4, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Doubrava, Kenneth J., Feb. 25, 1983-Mar. 5, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Doughty, Dorothy and Freda, ca.1945-1968 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Drabble, Margaret, May 28, 1986, Dec. 29, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Ducker, Lucy & Don, Oct. 21, 1967-Dec. 1978 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Dufour Editions, Feb. 11, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Duran, Flora [Mrs. Steve], Dec. 6, 1968, Mar. 19, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Durrant's Press Cuttings, Jan. 24, 1934 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - A. P. Dutton & Co., Aug. 25-Nov. 11, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Dydo, Ulla [letter of Oct. 11, 1982 includes copy of a draft Gertrude Stein letter to Laura Riding], Aug. 7, 1982-Oct. 27, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Dyke, Melissa, Dec. 26, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - East River Review, Oct. 6, 1977-June 19, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Eby, Clara, Oct. 29, 1969-Aug. 10, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Edhasa (Editoria y Distribuidora Hispano Americana), Apr. 19, 1985-Feb. 1, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Elegante, Mar. 3, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Ellidge, Honor, See: Wyatt, Honor (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Ellidge, Philip, Feb. 10-Mar. 15, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Emerson, Abbott, May 24, 1970-Dec. 1975 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Emery Collegiate Institute, Aug. 11, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Empson, William, Aug. 25, 1970-Apr. 29, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Enbanks, Hazel, July 6, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Encyclopaedia Britannica, Apr. 23-May 31, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Engelhardt, Herbert, Sept. 11, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 7)